Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
And with
approximately 140 tons
of overripened tomatoes.
La Tomatina remains the world's
greatest annual food fight.
Throwing it back to
you at the studio.
We'll ketchup later.
Ooh. Ouch.
-That was painful.
-What?
All right. that wasn't my best
tomato pun. but it was vine.
Wasn't it. Francis?
You know. boss. you don't
need to give a fake broadcast.
You know we're on
a mission. right?
Okay. easy.
You have your process.
I have mine. Simple.
Now let's zip it and keep
our eyes peeled for Gradov.
Seriously. Coop. the "ketchup"
line was strong. yeah?
Noel. as your oldest friend.
I can definitively say
that was not punny.
That's why I don't go big game
hunting without you CIA boys.
Speaking of. we got a
lion in the crosshairs.
Gray hat and jacket. pink
shirt. heading southwest.
matching the
target's description.
Walk faces and run it.
Okay. pink shirt. pink shirt.
Okay. I got him.
But I can't confirm it's Gradov.
Cho. you got anything?
That's a negative.
No-go for facial recognition.
Wait. I think I'm
staring right at him.
20 feet from me.
right below you. Coop.
What?
Ah. shit.
Guys. we got two
potential Gradovs on site.
Three.
Shit.
He's got decoys in play.
Stay on your mark. Jacks.
Talk to me. home base.
Still no facial recall.
It's like they know where
our cameras are positioned.
Get me gait analysis.
We'd have to request
a patch to Echelon.
Then request the patch!
Director Adams?
We have a request for
a real-time patch.
It's a joint MI6-CIA capture
of a high-value target.
-How high?
-NSA priority.
Russian arms dealer
Viktor Gradov.
First sighting in
over two years.
Noel. target one is still
in the southwest corner.
Coop. I don't like this van.
Field. you're authorized
for a 60-second link
to Echelon's servers.
All the time I need to
pin the real Gradov.
It's a VW T5. Spanish plates.
registered to a rental
company in Madrid.
What are you?
Field team. abort!
We've been set up!
Done.
Don't move.
Drop it.
♪ Sugar ♪
♪ Oh. honey. honey ♪
♪ You are my... ♪
U.S. President Will Derringer.
amidst soaring popularity
at home and abroad.
touched down in
London yesterday.
Derringer has stopped in
the U.K. for a brief visit
before he heads to a
NATO summit in Italy...
...president will be attending
a press conference in his
first face-to-face meeting
with the increasingly embattled
Prime Minister Sam Clarke.
now serving his sixth
year in office...
...Derringer smashed
worldwide box office records
playing the Venom in Denim
with his Water Cobra franchise.
He then went from bullets
flying to tears flowing
with his heartfelt
baseball drama
Sliding into Home...
We did it. son.
Made Mom proud.
...earning him a Golden
Globe nomination...
After only five
months in office.
Derringer is enjoying
historic polling numbers
and voter confidence.
With your help. we did
it at the box office.
and now we will do it
at the Oval Office.
No.
Good morning.
Mr. Prime Minister.
Here's your brief for
Thursday the 29th.
The economic minister will
announce record low unemployment.
The refugee crisis in Poland
continues to intensify.
with numbers growing into
the tens of thousands.
Your early-morning
meetings have been cleared
for an urgent briefing on a
classified intelligence op
in Spain that ended in tragedy.
Seven CIA and MI6
operatives have been killed.
Sam. I regret to say that team
leader Noel Bisset is missing
and presumed dead.
I'm so sorry.
Families of the fallen
are being notified...
You okay. boss?
And while the royals play host to the
American president and his family.
record crowds are gathered. hoping
for a glimpse of Will Derringer.
proving he's as loved
abroad as he is at home.
I just don't understand what
tornado has to do with anything.
Not tornados.
NATO. okay?
It's like. um. a-a
group of friends.
Let's say. in this
case. countries.
They-they get together. and
they make a pinky promise
if they ever see a bully.
let's say this guy.
and the bully
attacks one of them.
they all got to join in
and stand up to that bully.
And that's when they start
dropping warheads on foreheads.
Hey. what?
Who let her watch Water Cobra?
-I saw it at Janey's house.
-Oh. you did?
Hmm. Okay. well.
Janey's mom is now
-under federal investigation.
-Sir.
Scoot.
What time's the
lecture at Cambridge?
Not till 4:00.
Meet you at Trieste
in the morning?
-Yeah.
-Enjoy this.
And use it as a bonding opportunity
with the prime minister.
Please.
Don't tell me you're still mad
about the fish and chips thing.
He endorsed my opponent in
the heat of the campaign.
He had lunch with the guy.
It's hardly an endorsement.
Wasn't just lunch. It
was fish and chips.
Look. you got off
on the wrong foot.
-Sam's not a bad guy.
-It's not about bad or good.
He doesn't respect me.
This is where you're supposed
to say. "Yes. he does."
-He respects you.
-Way too late.
Is a man who got 83 million
votes from the American people
not feeling properly respected?
See you tomorrow.
Did you look over your speech?
Yeah. It's solid.
I'll hit it with some fireworks.
It'll crackle.
It's gonna be a good morning.
Won't be that simple.
Tell me.
Sideways op. Spain.
-Who was the target?
-Viktor Gradov.
Russian-born arms
dealer turned extremist.
Right. Black market
weapons developer
who got his hands on enriched
plutonium a few years back.
Yeah. that's when we
took him out of business.
Destroyed his manufacturing plant
with the help of a NATO task force.
We launched an air strike.
destroyed his whole facility.
After that. Gradov
went off the grid.
Spain was our first chance
to move on Gradov in two years.
Where is he now?
In the wind.
NSA is scraping border entries
and airport screenings for noise.
Intelligence and Research
didn't have the chance
-to do their usual analysis.
-Bloody hell.
How many times
I've got to say it?
We do not leapfrog intel.
About Noel. if you
want to talk...
I don't.
We should warn Clarke's
team about Jack Gordon.
Jack always goes
for the jugular.
and he will fry us
over this Spain thing.
Did you tell the
president's comms director
that he must stick
to the script?
-Yes.
-Good.
Hopefully he doesn't start
writing checks that we can't cash.
He still hasn't figured
out the difference between
a press conference
and a press junket.
Oh.
-Mr. Prime Minister.
-Mr. President.
Yeah. We finally meet.
You know. it was a shame that
you missed the inauguration.
It was a hell of a show.
-Sure it was.
-Yeah.
Well...
Shall we?
Uh. wait. wait.
We should savor this moment.
I mean. this is...
it's our debut duet.
-Duet?
-Yeah.
It's like I'm Dr. Dre
and you're Eminem.
and we're taking that stage
for the first time together.
I'm Eminem?
Listen. um. about this
terrible situation
-in Spain.
-Mm-hmm?
If it comes up out there.
I'd just steer clear of it.
-Let's just punt it.
-Punt it?
-Yeah.
-To where?
Well. to later.
Today's about NATO. clean
energy. light and bright stuff.
Light and bright. Okay.
You want to warm up together?
Do some breathing exercises?
I'm already breathing.
-Roger that. Well...
-Yeah.
Let's dance. I guess.
Hey. uh. just do us
both a favor out there.
No questions from Jack Gordon.
My guy.
And as of today.
thanks to this
revolutionary new technology
developed by both of
our great nations.
we are now partners in energy.
The pebble-bed reactor is not just
an investment in clean energy.
It's also an
investment in security.
Energy security is
national security.
It is also an investment
in job creation.
A whole lot of jobs.
And we no longer have to
deal with the Russians.
the Saudis or the
Venezuelans on oil.
But we are keen to present
this global initiative
to our NATO partners
in the coming days.
Okay. Questions?
President Derringer!
Uh. it's just been
announced that Water Cobra
is being expanded into
a cinematic universe.
Any chance you'll
be making a cameo?
Oh. folks.
I promised the first lady
if I ever dressed up as
the Venom in Denim again.
it'd either be in
the Oval boudoir
or for the White House
Correspondents' Dinner.
and you're only invited
to the last one.
Prime Minister Clarke.
-Yes?
-The Daily Mail have photos
of the duchess and a new beau.
Any comments about your
ex-girlfriend's latest escapades?
Okay. Who has a real question?
Hey. hold on a minute.
Now. who else is tired of seeing
the prime minister as a single man?
I'll tell you what.
How about we get him his
own season of The Bachelor?
Who's with me?
Yeah! Let's do it!
Jack Gordon.
There are six dead British and
Americans in Spain this morning.
Can you comment on
speculation this is the result
of a failed covert operation to capture
known arms dealer Viktor Gradov?
Covert operations are
covert for a reason.
That's all I'm
gonna say on that.
That and Gradov's gonna wish
we caught him yesterday.
Because when we do
get our hands on him.
he is going to be forming
a special relationship
with the concept of retribution.
We should also be using this as a
collective moment of introspection.
find out what went
wrong and learn from it.
Leaks indicate that Echelon
was accessed during the op.
Are you ready to acknowledge the existence
of a top secret surveillance program
which monitors all of our emails.
video conferences. phone calls...
Tom.
There's only so many times I
can say "no comment" to that.
I'll comment.
Our enemies should be afraid.
We have the tools and
we have the technology
to find and destroy them
if they challenge us.
We aren't making any
promises except that
we will work tirelessly
to get results.
Well. we are.
The United States of America
is promising results.
President Derringer.
do you have a message for the families
of the men and women killed in Spain?
I've spent a lot of time
with Special Forces.
Trained with them.
learned from them.
And what I have to say
is we must do better.
We will do better.
When you say. um.
"trained with them."
that was for an
acting role. yes?
Yes. but. uh...
I mean. y-you've never served.
As someone who did serve
in the British Army.
as most of you know.
if I did have something
to say to the families.
I would say it to them directly.
I do not salute heroes
through you. Jack.
To be clear. you
never saw combat.
But with all due respect.
gentlemen. you're politicians.
You don't equate yourselves
with actual heroes. do you?
Well. that was a shit-bath.
Socials are lighting up.
Hashtag "commanders
in beef" is trending.
Goddamn it!
You knew Jack
Gordon was trouble.
I warned you.
My town. I'll call
on whomever I want.
Let's take five.
You know. I'm not
afraid of the press.
Not all of us have a compulsive
need to be liked by everyone.
With all due respect...
I know you like to fight
his battles for him. Simone.
Your presidency is in diapers.
You're on a learning curve.
-I've been on this slog for six years.
-You?
I fight my own battles. You.
you want to talk numbers?
Your approval ratings. that's
a great place to start.
Unlike you. I'll take results
over likes on Instagram.
You-you clearly don't care
about what people think.
You called for a collective
moment of introspection?
Let's just say I'm more concerned
with how people pay their mortgages
and send their
kids to university.
Oh. for sure. 'cause God knows
there's nothing the public loves more
than politicians
giving them homework.
Is this about the
fish and chips thing?
'Cause if it is. just say it.
I am not mad about the
goddamn fish and chips thing.
Enough. Neither of you
were at your best today.
Agreed.
We need to give this
a short shelf life.
He's right. Change
the narrative.
Turn this into an opportunity.
To show that you
guys are united.
I've got it.
You fly to Trieste
together on Air Force One.
I don't know if we
have enough room.
No. I'm good. thank
you very much.
And besides. I have to
be in Warsaw tonight.
Hear me out. all right?
You both do 35 seconds on the
air stairs here in London.
waving and smiling.
pit stop in Warsaw.
You'll be in Trieste
by breakfast.
By that time. pictures of
you on those air stairs.
a vision of solidarity.
will be on the front page of
eight out of ten newspapers
all around the world.
Quincy.
Bradshaw.
I am the President
of the United States.
I don't share the
stage with anyone.
Hitch a ride? Is
that your solution?
It's a guaranteed three-point
bump in the polls.
Look. we are in the early days.
You've got to show
you can make friends.
Right now we need him
more than he needs us.
Sam. take the win.
Take the flight.
Will you be there?
I'll go with the advance team.
Quincy and I will foam the
runway with the press in Trieste.
Mr. Prime Minister.
Would you do me the honor and
fly with me aboard Air Force One?
I'll be honest.
It kept me up all night.
How is it that I hire the
best sniper money can buy
and he misses the one
shot meant to protect
the most important man
in my entire operation?
Yeah. thanks. but we're
all just doing our part.
Pieces of a puzzle.
patches on a quilt...
I assumed it was
faulty equipment.
But now I know it
was human error.
Like you say...
"Everything that happens
happens for the best."
Yes.
Come.
Sit down.
My mother was very
fond of that phrase.
Yes.
She was a gadalka.
A fortune teller.
She read tea leaves.
She could see the future.
She saw mine and
said that one day
I would be served
a great injustice.
and it would be my mission in
life to punish those responsible.
And nothing or no one
would get in my way.
It's been over a decade
since a U.S. president
has hosted a British prime
minister on Air Force One.
making this trip one
for the history books.
Check her out.
Fresh off the assembly line.
30-foot wider wingspan
than the previous model.
Can break Mach 1. oh.
and corners like an F-15.
Surprised you didn't paint
flames on the side of it.
Ah. you're just jealous 'cause your
plane sucks and doesn't have a cool name.
Fellas.
We love Will! We love Will!
Mr. Prime Minister.
I heard you like rye.
This one comes from my
hometown in Kentucky.
Mmm.
Now. that is American
exceptionalism in action.
Thank you.
Enjoy. sir.
There he is. Come on.
Say hello to Prime
Minister Clarke. Hey.
Be nice to him. Sawyer. He's
besties with Harry Styles.
Well. I don't know about that.
but next time he's in Washington.
I'll see if I can get
you some good seats.
-Thank you.
Nice to finally meet
you. Mr. Prime Minister.
Now. honestly.
just-just call me Sam.
I'm so sorry we
missed each other.
You two take care of yourselves.
and go easy on him. Sam.
We're still learning the ropes.
I'll try and keep
him out of trouble.
Okay. hey.
Love you guys. Talk
to you tomorrow.
You're good at that.
Good at what?
Being normal. Ish.
Uh. thank you?
You should show people that
side of you more often.
Start by ditching
the bachelor status.
World leader who's unmarried?
Freaks people out. leaves
too much to the imagination.
What are they imagining?
I don't know. Eyes
Wide Shut parties
or by night you're some masked vigilante
into some weird. unsettling shit.
Look. people want clarity.
Marriage gives them clarity.
It softens the image.
I'm confused. Are
you giving me advice
or are you pitching me on
one of your shit rom-come?
All right. I get it. You
don't like my movies.
I've never seen your movies.
Because Sam Clarke is the man who
does not like to be entertained.
No. it's 'cause I
like actual cinema.
Come on.
You don't think I wanted
to work with Wes Anderson
or Bong Joon Ho? Of course I do.
I'm classically trained.
Did you know I once did a
play with Edward Norton?
Mm.
But the universe keeps telling me
I look cool with a gun in my hand.
A toy gun.
What is it with you?
Walking around. thinking you're
better than everybody else.
First. thought it
was a British thing.
Then I realized
it's a you thing.
-I know Paul McCartney. okay?
-Wow.
He's put a whole lot more
wins on the board than you.
and he is cool as shit!
-Want me to take it up?
-I got it. Thanks.
And you know what?
I'm not gonna apologize for
wanting to be liked or loved.
We're blessed with two of
the most extraordinary jobs
ever created. and part of
that job is to instill hope.
It's to make people feel good.
Yeah. well. based on
my experience. okay.
hope is just delayed
disappointment.
Doesn't put food on the table.
Doesn't put a roof
over anyone's head.
And if you want to focus on
making people "feel good."
then you're never gonna
understand how to help them.
You are the commander in chief.
You're not some DJ in Vegas.
I don't need to be
refreshed on my job title.
Let's be clear about that.
Don't tell the captain
I snuck you his stash.
Thanks.
Move to intercept.
Just know. once this
honeymoon period is over.
there is only disappointment
in your future.
because this job. my
job. is about suffering.
Yeah. Nostradamus?
When that day comes. maybe
then you and I can sit down
and talk about it over
some fish and chips.
I knew the truth would come out.
There it is.
Oh. great. You did
it. Agatha Christie.
You cracked the case.
Let's give Scooby
Snacks to everybody.
Will. let it go.
You took my opponent for fish
and chips in broad daylight
in the middle of
"Liester" Square.
and you knew photographers
would be there!
First of all. it's
pronounced Leicester Square.
And. no. bollocks.
he's an old friend.
I took him for lunch.
You knew there were
political implications.
Not all of us have some posh
Cambridge Mafia in Parliament
helping us get elected!
I busted my ass to
get to where I am.
I was born in a housing estate
and was never given anything
on a silver platter.
I worked three jobs
to pay for Cambridge.
and then to the Army. and
then to community organizing.
and then Defence Attaché. and
worked my way up through Parliament.
Now. not all of us got
our political start
because some commercial
agent decided they like
-our G.I. Joe jawline!
-Watch it!
No. no. no! You went from modeling your
underwear to being on the red carpet
to having your finger
on the nuclear button.
all without doing a single
day of public service!
So. yes. mate. when I see you
play the role of president.
it makes me sick to my stomach.
because you know your lines...
oh. yes. you do... but you're
not believable in the part.
And if I could've endorsed
your opponent. yes. I would've.
because at least there'd be a
real leader in the White House
and not some embarrassing.
bullshit. popcorn president!
-What's that?
-You heard what I said!
No. what's that?
Sirs. secure yourselves
in the office.
-Fasten your seat belts. Sir.
-Yeah?
Take your seat. please.
-What's happening?
-Unidentified aircraft.
you're in restricted airspace.
Pull away immediately or
you will be fired upon.
All radios are out.
Comms are fried
across the board.
Dear God.
-Ready the weapons.
-Yes. sir.
Oh. shit.
Uh. gentlemen.
Multiple inbound bogies!
Open fire!
Mr. President! Sir!
What the hell's going on?
Shit. We got to get to
the back of the plane! Go!
Go! Go!
Stop shooting the drones!
Shoot the goddamn plane!
Hold on!
Initiating emergency descent to 10.000
for cabin pressure stabilization.
Let's go!
There are parachutes
in the back!
Here comes another wave.
We lost engine two.
Gonna lean into it.
Come on. we got to jump!
That way! Through the door!
Come on. sir! Move!
We're leveling out.
They're finished.
Let's go home.
Let's go!
Come on! Let's move! Quick!
These two should be intact.
Shit!
We're going down in
Belarusian airspace.
You'll need to get to
our safe house in Poland.
Rip it hard once you're out.
The chute'll do the rest.
We can double up.
Not a chance. Too risky.
What about all these people?
We all have our jobs to do.
Yours is to survive.
Get to Golden Mountain
Mining Company
under the Gdanski
Bridge in Warsaw.
Let me hear it. sirs.
Golden Mountain Mining Company.
Gdanski Bridge!
It's been an honor.
Mr. President.
Oh. shit.
We have just received
devastating footage
of Air Force One going
down over Western Belarus.
President William Derringer and
Prime Minister Samuel Clarke...
are presumed dead.
We're awaiting word
from the Pentagon
on the potential
cause or suspects.
No groups are claiming
responsibility for this tragic loss.
An emergency session of
Parliament is convening
to discuss succession strategy.
while moments ago V.P.
Elizabeth Kirk was sworn in
as acting president
in Trieste. Italy.
...where gathering NATO leaders
are offering their condolences
and unyielding solidarity.
What was meant to be a celebration
of the North Atlantic Alliance
is now a time of unprecedented
shock and mourning.
Oh. geez.
You okay?
Yeah. You?
How the hell'd they
get on my plane?
With the help of someone on
the inside. that's for sure.
The Polish border is
about 15 miles that way.
On foot. we can be at that
safe house by morning.
No. The cavalry's coming.
Cavalry's not coming. mate.
Belarus will want to
control the crash site.
Won't be letting any
planes into their airspace.
and there's no way our guys
are sneaking across enemy lines
to retrieve corpses.
They have to assume
there are no survivors.
Shit.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
What are you doing?
Calling my wife. I'm
letting her know I'm alive.
No. No. no. no. no.
No. No phones.
All right? Do as I do.
We just survived the worst
security breach in history.
so you have to assume
whoever wants you dead
is listening to
communications. okay?
I'm calling my family to
let them know I'm okay.
And we should let the
world know we're okay.
We're not okay.
All right? If we fall
into the wrong hands.
They use us as a
political football.
Worst-case scenario is...
They make an example of us.
Now put that down!
You know what happened to the last guy
who threw a shoe at a sitting president?
You're not sitting.
You're hanging.
All right?
You know what? Piss off.
You want me to piss off?
-Yeah.
-Okay. I'll piss off.
I'll piss off all
the way to Warsaw.
Enjoy living the rest of your
life as a bird sanctuary.
All right. don't piss off.
Would you just help me down
for Chrissakes. please?
There you go. Look at that.
An American action hero
asking me for help.
Even in his most noble moments. he
was still petty and mean-spirited.
I'm gonna drop you on three.
Three!
You all right back
there. Derringer?
I'm fine.
Hearing a lot of
panting and snuffling.
I don't snuffle. okay?
Besides. don't concern yourself
with how another man breathes.
Boundaries. guy.
Nothing to be embarrassed about.
Endurance is tough
for guys like you.
Guys like me?
Guys like you. You
know. gym strong.
-Gym strong?
-Gym strong.
As opposed to?
-Strong strong.
-Want to see gym strong?
I'll rip a tree out of the ground
and beat you to death with it. huh?
-Go on. then.
-What?
Rip that tree out and
beat me to death with it.
That's what I thought.
Silly thing to say. really.
Picked the biggest tree.
Dear God.
Think he's had the day off.
Who the hell did this?
We got a lot of enemies.
Right now we got to get
home alive. That's our job.
No. our real job is to find out
who did this and make them pay.
Look. I want to get them
just as much as you do.
but these things don't
happen overnight.
We got to pick our moment.
Took us ten years and two
wars before we got bin Laden.
I'm not waiting ten years.
One thing for certain. whoever
did this got some big balls.
There's no reason to think
this wasn't just phase one.
Tell the Pentagon to
move DEFCON status up.
and inform Russia. China and Iran this
is not a moment to get adventurous.
Don't challenge us and don't
think we're distracted.
-Yes?
-Echelon is standing by
-for system security update.
-Please.
This is Kirk.
This is Echelon Director Adams.
Please confirm voice
print and retinal scan.
Alpha. Echo. Bravo.
Alpha. Charlie.
Zulu. Tango.
Voiceprint confirmed.
Biometrics confirmed.
Commence continuity of
government protocol.
Sir.
What's happening?
They're rebooting the system.
In three. two. one.
Almost there.
Someone's inside the system.
Uh. wh-what's happening?
We are now in
control of Echelon.
Now we're talking.
There's our ride to Warsaw.
We can't just walk down
and ask them for a lift.
I'd agree with you.
but you're wrong.
We can.
We're two of the most
recognizable men on the planet.
Ha. You're not even one of the
most recognizable British people.
You get my point.
The point is we need help.
we ask them for help.
What part of "keep our heads
down" don't you understand?
-You got a better idea?
-Yeah. I do.
I say we move fast. creep
along that tree line
and hot-wire that
car over there.
Since when do you
know how to hot-wire?
I don't. but you do.
You got busted at 16 for
stealing your neighbor's Camaro.
Where'd you hear about that?
I vetted you.
You vetted me?
I'm the President of
the United States.
You don't vet me. I vet you.
Well. did you vet me?
-Not the point.
-Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
Yeah. there he is.
Boys.
Oh. no.
We have incoming.
I'm going to talk to them.
-They'll give us a ride.
-No. no. no.
You're gonna start this car.
and we're gonna get out of here.
Trust me. I poll really well
with young men who drink beer.
I speak their language.
Except you literally don't
speak their language.
Cinema is the
international language.
-Watch the magic.
-Will. Hey.
Hey. fellas. how's it going?
We got a little turned around.
We could use some help.
It's me. Will Derringer.
You know. Water Cobra.
Huh. still nothing?
Nice watch.
-Huh?
-I think you should give him the watch.
Let me try it on.
This is a gift from Keanu
when we wrapped Carnage 2.
Yeah. well. I hope Keanu gifted
you some kung fu lessons.
'cause we're about to
get our asses kicked.
Man. read the room.
See?
That's enough!
On your right!
Oh. sorry.
Don't.
Stop!
I said. stop!
What have you done?
You are dead men.
Hey!
Ah. God.
You okay?
Get your asses home!
You half-witted cretins!
Yankees?
No. no. no. Canadians.
Why'd you say Canadians?
Everybody loves Americans.
Americans love Americans.
Today we're Canadians.
Trust me.
Where you go?
Across the border to Warsaw.
Papers?
No papers.
Okay.
I take you.
I have great ride.
♪ Hang me. oh. hang me ♪
♪ I'll be dead and gone ♪
♪ Wouldn't mind the hanging ♪
♪ but the laying in the
grave so long. poor boy ♪
♪ I've been all
around this world ♪
Eh. it'll be great
for our memoirs.
"Chapter 14.
It was exactly like when Churchill
met FDR for the first time.
just with an added
splash of sheep shit."
Could be worse.
We're experiencing the
kindness of a stranger.
We're en route to safety.
Shortly after we get there.
we'll make our enemies feel
the ripple of our wrath.
Is-is that the...
Battle cry of the
central character
in one of the most
seminal action franchises
in the last decade? Hell yeah.
What?
What do you Brits know
about slogans anyway?
"Keep calm and carry on."
You know. that-that's
actually like saying.
"Do nothing and continue
to do nothing." right?
Yeah. we don't all fetishize
tag lines to the same degree.
-Oh. yeah?
-Yeah.
Well. here's what
I don't get. okay?
If life is such a Möbius
strip of failure and futility.
why would you want to
lead an entire nation?
I just like sitting
in musty old rooms.
arguing with boring
old men about tax code.
-Okay?
-That's a good one.
Seriously.
Why would you want to run for
highest office in the land?
Yeah. fine. Me first.
Did you know I didn't
travel outside the U.S.
until I was 28 years old?
First Water Cobra press tour.
And it was there I realized. man.
there are awesome people everywhere.
But the world is
so damn fractured.
So I figured if I could use my
celebrity. even just for a little bit.
to bring people together.
wouldn't that be a good thing?
Okay. What's your excuse?
Certainly not about believing you'd
deliver people to better days.
I believe in better days.
In fact. this day has got
me believing in better days
more than any other day.
because any day would be better
than being stuck in the muck
with you and a bunch of...
You having a rough one. huh?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Take it up with your
security detail.
Or my security detail.
Or anybody on that flight.
Down. down. down. down. down.
Passports and documents
for the livestock.
Kill the engine and get out.
Maybe we could make a deal?
What?
♪ Went up on the mountain ♪
♪ There I made my stand ♪
Think I'm ready to
write those memoirs now.
♪ There I made my stand ♪
♪ Rifle on my shoulder ♪
♪ and a dagger in my hand ♪
♪ Poor boy. I've been
all around this world ♪
Thank you.
Take this.
It was my pleasure...
Mr. President.
Good luck to both of you.
Sir. Echelon intercepted
security footage
from a CIA safe house in Warsaw
that just buzzed in two guests.
With all due respect.
we got what we needed when
we took down Air Force One.
Quiet your mouth.
And we kept our footprint tight.
so who cares if they live?
They die because I say they die.
They're alive. Warsaw.
Warsaw! Let's go!
You're alive.
Oh.
Okay. Hey.
-Are you crying because of me?
-Hell yeah. I am. man.
I mean. sir.
I'm sorry. Marty Comer.
Oh. well.
Station agent.
A huge fan.
Patriot.
Sam Clarke. British
prime minister.
-Can we come in?
-Yeah.
Yeah. of course. of course.
Like. now?
-Yeah. now.
-Thank you.
Right this way.
Okay. so I know this
sounds. uh. bonkers. but...
What's the playbook on this?
For this?
Th-There is no damn playbook.
I mean... And we got
lots of playbooks.
Ones that account
for pole shifts.
computers becoming self-aware.
space monkey attacks.
all kinds of hectic shit.
But. uh. none that contemplate
you two sauntering in here
after dying in front of
the entire planet's eyes.
So no playbook?
Let's make one.
They say never meet your
heroes. but to them I say:
You've never met President
William Matthew Derringer.
Your initials are WMD?
Yeah. Pretty bitchin'. right?
Follow me. gentlemen.
Your timing's great. by the way.
The ambassador just recalled all
in-country personnel to the embassy.
It's a real nut punch in
a Ziploc bag out there.
And it ain't exactly a
coincidence. if you ask me.
W-Wait. what's not?
Well. first you two go down.
and then someone rolls a political
grenade into that NATO conference.
You guys didn't hear?
No. we've had a pretty busy day.
Well. apparently.
Echelon servers
were infiltrated.
Two hours ago.
a tranche of classified
documents were leaked.
exposing decades of covert
activity amongst NATO members:
industrial espionage. economic sabotage
and the influencing of foreign elections.
And the real pisser?
These weren't acts committed against
enemy nations but against each other.
These were friends
against friends.
I'm talking some real Monica
and Rachel season two shit.
I mean. tomorrow's summit's
gonna be a monkey knife fight
in a telephone booth.
Germany just found out
France embedded journalists
to influence their
last election.
The Czech Republic wants Italy
kicked out of the building
for trying to tank
their economy.
All while we're locked out of the most
powerful surveillance tool on this planet.
How many files are
we talking about?
20.000 and counting.
It's the most damaging leak
of state secrets in history.
Someone is using Echelon to
tear at the very fabric of NATO.
Sounds like NATO has been
tearing at the fabric of itself.
Bet you're dying to
say "I told you so."
Excuse me?
You ran your primaries
on "America first."
Simone. I am allowing you to be in
this room out of respect for Will.
Allowing me?
But please don't ever insinuate that
I'm not all in on this alliance.
If NATO falls. there's no more
backstop against despots and dictators.
They run unchecked.
It could set off a series
of events that-that would
destabilize Europe and
the rest of the world.
We are talking about the potential
for increased conflict. chaos
and the very real threat
of war on a global scale.
We put our heads above water.
Call the embassy. Let
them know you have us.
No. we have to assume all high
command posts are compromised.
Bullshit.
We are in a secure
U.S. facility.
You guys want a hit
of these Pringles?
Last time I was in one of those. we
got shot out of the sky at 40.000 feet.
Hmm?
Make the call.
-Mm-hmm.
-Don't make the call.
Make the call.
-Hmm.
-Don't make the call.
-I can't make the call.
-I'm the commander in chief!
-Make the goddamn call.
-The line's dead.
Is that normal?
No.
Somebody really wants us dead.
We're safe. we're in
a safe house. right?
We got this.
That feel safe enough for you?
Shit.
Not in the movies now. son.
Okay. listen up.
I'm gonna get you guys out of here.
but just in case things do go south.
best to beat a retreat
through the secondary exit.
That's a left out of here.
down the hall. make a left.
That's the bunk room.
Another right. you should
see a poster on the wall.
You punch through that poster.
you should be good to go.
Feed me. boys.
♪ I can't stand it ♪
♪ I know you planned it ♪
♪ I'm-a set it straight.
this Watergate ♪
♪ I can't stand rocking
when I'm in here ♪
♪ 'cause your crystal ball
ain't so crystal clear ♪
♪ So while you sit
back and wonder why ♪
♪ I got this...
thorn in my side ♪
♪ Oh. my God ♪
♪ It's a mirage.
I'm telling y'all ♪
♪ it's sabotage ♪
♪ So. so. so ♪
♪ So listen up 'cause
you can't say nothing...
All of you in here! Now!
♪ I'm out and I'm gone ♪
♪ I'll tell you now.
I keep it on and on ♪
♪ 'Cause what you see...
That boy's a nutter.
Maybe. but he's
America's nutter.
♪ That's a mirage ♪
♪ I'm trying to tell you
now. it's sabotage...
Let's move.
♪ Listen. all y'all ♪
♪ it's a sabotage ♪
♪ Listen all y'all.
it's a sabotage ♪
♪ I can't stand it. I
know you planned it ♪
♪ I'm-a set it straight.
this Watergate ♪
♪ Lord. I can't stand rocking
when I'm in this place ♪
♪ because I feel disgrace
because you're all in my face ♪
♪ But make no mistakes
and switch up my channel ♪
♪ I'm Buddy Rich when
I fly off the handle ♪
♪ What could it be?
It's a mirage...
Get out of here.
♪ That's sabotage ♪
Go!
Come on!
No. no. this way. He said right!
Damn it!
No. no. Rambo! Come on!
Oh. found the poster.
Punch it.
Oh. goddamn it.
-What's the problem?
-I can't.
You having a laugh?!
Come on!
Forgive me.
I think I killed that guy.
Only thing you
killed is the wall.
I have to say. though.
you do look good with
a gun in your hand.
-You should go.
-No. you go.
Drop your guns!
We have them.
Coming down.
Noel?
Sam?
-I thought you were dead.
How are you not dead?
You two know each other?
-We...
-We worked together. Back in the day.
How'd you find us?
All right. I'll tell you!
Hey! Hey!
Long story.
Hey. where's your backup?
There is no backup.
I've been trailing
Gradov since Spain.
-Victor Gradov is behind this?
-The gun guy? -Mm-hmm.
So you're saying
this is all payback
because we stopped
him building nukes?
That way. Gradov
wasn't building a nuke.
But he was a weapons developer.
He was. but his son wasn't.
Yeah. what's his son
got to do with it?
His son was a scientist.
He was brilliant and made
incredible breakthroughs.
He was on the brink of on lining
the first ever nuclear reactor
incapable of melting down.
The pebble-bed technology.
Our pebble-bed technology?
The same technology I just told
the world that we developed?
You're telling me
Gradov's son invented it?
He was close.
He still needed the
enriched plutonium.
which his father procured
from the black market.
Echelon picked up
on that transaction.
Of course we assumed it
was to build a weapon.
So we did what one does when
faced with a nuclear threat.
You dropped warheads
on foreheads?
We did.
Gradov's son was
amongst the dead.
The operation was
sanctioned by NATO.
We couldn't risk the chance
that he was building a nuke.
Millions of lives were at stake.
It was only in the aftermath we realized
what was actually being developed.
So with the help of Echelon.
we procured the schematics
for the pebble-bed tech.
Get back.
So we took his son's life
and then his legacy. huh?
Which we were about to take a
big victory lap for in Trieste.
Correct me if I'm
doing the math wrong.
-but we're the assholes here.
-Okay. look.
Gradov's son didn't
die because of us.
He died because he's
the son of the devil.
Let's keep it moving.
Gradov couldn't
have done all this
without top-level
security clearance.
Okay. so then the question is: Who
was Gradov working with on the inside?
Got to start with the guy who
put us both in that plane.
What?
You weren't supposed
to fly with me.
Somebody put that idea in
your head. insisted on it.
Quincy.
A safe house was hit in Warsaw.
What are you thinking?
Could be Will and Sam?
There must have been something
in there worth going after.
We have to consider
the possibility...
Did you not see
what we all saw?
They went down
with Air Force One.
I'm not giving up hope. Not yet.
None of us should be.
We need to focus all our
energies on this Echelon leak.
The rhetoric is heating up.
But if there's even a chance that
Will and Sam are still alive...
We put CIA on the
safe house in Warsaw.
And right here in this building.
the focus is on stopping
the bleeding with NATO.
I want an audience with Italy. Germany
and France as soon as possible.
It's time these guys stopped
clutching their pearls
and get on with the
business of leading.
It's my son. Excuse me.
Hi. sweetheart.
Simone. I appreciate how
much Will meant to you.
I know he was like a
brother. but he's gone.
They're both gone.
You need to start wrapping
your head around that.
-There's no way it's Quincy.
-How can you be sure?
He's been my chief of
staff for six years.
I known him since university.
The way normal people know him
or the way you know people?
Ah. don't start
that shit again.
Does he like bangers and
mash or fish and chips?
Ah. I see what you did there.
Sneaking the fish and chips
back into the conversation.
You must be exhausted
trying to figure that out.
Stop chipping away
at each other.
We need to be on the same page.
Did she just hit us with a pun?
She loves a pun.
I tried to tell her puns
are for simple people.
-I love puns.
-My point exactly.
Guys!
Over here.
Come on.
Look. right now the key
is getting to Trieste.
Trieste? How far away is
the U.S. embassy from here?
They can help us.
We're not going to the embassy.
Wait. why won't anyone
let me go to my embassy?
What does everybody suddenly
have against embassies?
We have to presume
that all high command
posts are compromised.
Say that again.
I'm gonna scream.
Not just a conventional
scream. a guttural wail.
Let's go.
Listen. I'm the
commander in chief.
Okay. respectfully.
sir. no. you're not.
The vice president was
sworn in a few hours ago.
And he has never been
commander in chief of anything.
The king is.
In fact. he's the only head of state
that's not an actual head of state.
Again. king.
You're just two guys that
are shit out of luck.
So let's go.
Come on.
♪ Turn around. bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and
then I fall apart...
You are now my package.
My mission.
And my mission is
to deliver you alive
to the most secure
location on this continent.
and that is the NATO
summit in Trieste.
And my best shot at keeping
this mission on track
is that train.
Pun. this time. not intended!
You seem very "locomotivated"!
Trying to make sure this thing
doesn't go off the rails!
Ha!
Well. that confirms it!
I died in that plane
crash. and this is hell!
♪ I don't know what to do.
and I'm always in the dark ♪
♪ We're living in
a powder keg...
Come on!
♪ I really need you tonight...
-You good?
-Thank you.
♪ Forever's gonna
start tonight ♪
♪ Once upon a time. I
was falling in love ♪
♪ now I'm only falling apart ♪
♪ Nothing I can say ♪
♪ A total eclipse
of the heart... ♪
About your team in Spain.
We've all lost a lot.
Look. I-I owe you a...
Please don't say an apology.
An explanation for
disappearing after Tripoli.
What happened in Tripoli?
None of your business.
Go back to sleep.
Okay. first of all. you
didn't disappear in Tripoli.
You appeared everywhere.
You were on TV.
newspapers. social media...
I was running for office.
You were running away.
Was it love?
Were you running away from love?
Can you stay in your lane?
And you could have come with me.
On the campaign trail?
Like. go on breakfast TV
and share my mom's lasagne
recipe with the world?
We would have been together.
No. Sam.
We couldn't have been together.
I'm gonna go get
something to eat.
Can I get you anything.
Mr. President?
I'll have whatever
you're having.
You got it.
I'm just gonna go
out on a limb here.
You two did a little more than
work together back in the day. huh?
I mean. she seems nice.
A lot better than that best
friend chief of staff of yours
that's a sleeper spy insurgent.
We're not having
this conversation.
Listen. man. she's a
little emotionally distant.
Great sense of humor. though.
Hey.
Why'd you guys split up?
And he's back.
Back to questions.
Come on. What
happened in Tripoli?
-Don't.
-Come on.
-What happened in Tripoli. Sam?
-Stop saying "Tripoli"!
Fine. what happened in
the capital city of Libya?
It's where I told her that
I wanted to run for office.
Are you happy now?
And why'd you want
to run for office?
Oh. God. are you still going?
Why'd you want to
run for office. Sam?
Because. because I wanted
to build a better world
for her and I to
grow old in together!
That's...
...the most romantic goddamn
thing I've ever heard.
Yeah. well. she didn't...
she didn't see it that way.
-Shit!
-Whoa. whoa. We can talk this out.
I know you're both enamored with
the sound of your own voice.
but there's no more talking.
What the hell?!
Oh. shit.
Didn't see that coming.
Already short on time as it is.
Drop it.
Whoa. hey.
-Don't shoot him.
-We need to hear him out.
You want to hear him out?
Let's do it on the move.
Come on.
All I wanted to do was
live my days out in peace.
but Gradov found me.
put his claws into me.
made me do things I
never wanted to do.
But what's happening now.
what we've set into motion
now. it's a bridge too far.
I know you've figured
out there's an insider
working at the highest
levels of government.
And. no. I...
I don't know...
I don't know who the insider is.
I never saw them face-to-face.
But they helped Gradov
get into Echelon.
and they helped him
take down Air Force One.
Then how do we find out
who this insider is?
Through Gradov's
secure communications.
Communications I designed.
But you'll have to get
off this train right now.
While it's moving?
Gradov's got the eyes
of God at his disposal.
They'll have a team waiting at
the next station to kill you.
-Great.
Look. there's a
building in Croatia
I operated out of before I
ever knew the name Gradov.
Get to 12 Lavaska
Street in Zadar.
There's a secure terminal
there on the fifth floor.
Give me your hand.
This prompt will run
a program I designed
to trace communications
he had with anyone
carrying compartmented
security clearance.
Run the program. you'll
find the insider.
You have to end this.
Gradov is insatiable.
He'll never stop.
Feels nice to do something
good for a change.
Shit. Okay.
Okay.
You know what? We
got this. okay?
Hell. I barrel-rolled off a
freight train in Death Jumpers.
No. you didn't.
Your stuntman did.
Now? Now you want to bust
me on a technicality?
Sir. respectfully. no one is
barrel-rolling off of this train.
I think it's time
to raise your heads.
-We have to call someone.
-No. no. no.
We have to assume that all high
command posts are compromised.
Yes. and if we resurface
now. the cover-up begins.
we never find out who's behind this.
and they get to fight another day.
So you'd rather jump off a train
that's going 40 miles an hour?
We've been taking this on
the chin for way too long.
and I'm done with
being on the defensive!
Oh! Come on!
All right. hey!
Just tuck your
chin to your chest!
Sure that's gonna
make a difference?
Trust me!
I think he's okay.
Damn you.
Man up. Derringer.
You're the President
of the United States.
Stars and stripes forever!
At the CIA. we had a saying:
"The strength of the
organization is the individual.
The strength of the individual
is the organization."
The collective that sits in this room
is the living embodiment of that.
And someone out there
is manipulating us.
Trying to tear us apart.
So let's send whoever's
behind this a message.
Swing in the other direction.
Double down on NATO.
Let it be known that if you
try and break this bond.
it will only make us stronger.
Those are lovely sentiments.
But what you're asking for
is predicated on trust.
And I don't trust
anyone in this room.
-Chancellor...
-It's fine.
Let him walk.
He's in a campaign
season. He's scared.
You know what I'm going to
campaign on in the next cycle?
Withdrawing from this alliance.
It's okay.
We can hold this together.
The U.S. will cover the
cost of their contribution.
That's what we all
need. isn't it?
I think so.
More American arrogance
shoved down our throats.
There will be a vote
held in the morning
with 25 countries already
on board to disband NATO.
including Italy.
I'll see you there.
Madam President.
Man. the chin thing
kind of worked. huh?
All right. enough with
the bloody chin thing.
You don't have a bloody chin
thanks to my killer pro tip.
Way to go. bro.
You made her mad.
Thanks.
Geez. Hammond didn't have an
incredibly sexy taste in hideouts. huh?
Well. some people like to hide
out in old derelict buildings.
and others like to
suck on sheep nipples.
-Who sucks on sheep nipples?
-Nobody sucks on sheep nipples!
Okay. God. Geez.
-What floor?
-Fifth.
All right.
Come on. Gym Strong.
There's nothing here.
Hammond. that lying
son of a bitch.
Led us to a dead end.
Unless...
...he didn't.
Well. nice.
Okay.
Do you hear that?
That does not look
like the cavalry!
Lock yourselves
in the safe room.
-I'm gonna go handle this.
-No. no. no.
You're the only one that can
get the intel off the server.
-I'll hold them off.
-Sam...
What. do you think
I've lost a step?
I know you've lost a step.
I just don't want you
dying on my watch.
Just go.
We got this.
You're coming with
me. I need your hand.
I've been shot!
You okay?
Yep!
Hand.
Okay.
Oh. shit.
Is he okay?
Yeah. he's holding them
off. but we need to go.
Come on. come on. come on.
Okay. we're in.
Abort!
Fall back!
-I got the insider.
-Yeah. it's Quincy.
It's Bradshaw.
Bullshit.
-Tell me where it says that.
-There are dozens
of communications between her and
Gradov going back almost 18 months.
Her digital fingerprints
are all over this.
-I'm sorry.
-You don't need to be sorry.
I'm gonna grind up her world
when I get my hands on...
It's stuck.
-You okay?!
-Yes!
Okay!
Sam.
We need to get out of this box.
I need you over here! Now!
-You see that roof?
-Yeah.
Get as low as you can. okay?
Get ready.
Drop!
It's handled.
She paid you extra to clean
up loose ends. didn't she?
And now I'm the loose end.
I'm sorry.
I know how much he meant to you.
We had this...
perfectly imperfect thing...
...that didn't fade
with time or distance.
Knowing that someone loves
everything about the way you are.
Well. except the puns.
Sam hated those puns.
Yeah.
You know. for a second there.
I thought that the
universe did all this shit.
all this horrible shit.
just to bring us back together.
And I was happy.
Pretty demented. huh?
I just found out my best
friend tried to kill me
and wants to rip the heart
out of Western democracy.
so everything's being
graded on a curve today.
Yeah.
...with a vote on
the future of NATO
set 30 minutes from now
and with world leaders
openly expressing their outrage and
anger at their allies and friends.
it seems imminent
that after 75 years. -
NATO is on the
verge of collapse.
Yes?
Madam President.
Thanks for keeping my seat warm.
Will? How did you...
-I'm coming in.
-Tell me what you need.
I'm at the Port of Trieste.
Send the Beast.
Oh. and. Kirk.
Bradshaw's behind this.
-so box her out.
-O-Okay.
Um. I-I'll hold off the
NATO vote as long as I can.
and-and just get here safe.
Mr. President.
You sure are a
sight for sore eyes.
-After you.
-Oh. thank you.
Thank you. everybody.
The meeting will
commence in 30 minutes.
Take them to the rally
point and do your job.
Don't disappoint me again.
It wasn't Bradshaw.
It's Kirk.
Of course it was
the vice president.
It's always the vice president.
Kirk has them.
Don't let them get to NATO.
But Bradshaw's communications
were tied to Gradov.
Bradshaw was the decoy.
Kirk covered her tracks.
It's called contingencies.
You have your contingencies.
I have mine.
♪ When I get high. I
get high on speed ♪
♪ Top Fuel funny
car's a drug for me ♪
♪ My heart. my heart ♪
♪ kick-start my heart ♪
♪ Always got the cops
coming after me ♪
♪ Custom-built bike doing 103 ♪
♪ My heart ♪
♪ My heart.
kick-start my heart...
We got company!
♪ Ooh. are you ready. girls? ♪
Shoot him!
Take the shot!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Kickstart my heart.
give it a start ♪
♪ Woah. yeah ♪
♪ Baby...
Oh. sh-shit.
-Take the wheel!
-Okay!
♪ Kick-start my heart.
hope it never stops ♪
♪ Woah. yeah ♪
♪ Baby. yeah...
Yeah!
Ha!
♪ Kick-start my heart...
-Sam?
Hold her steady!
Okay. no problem!
♪ My heart. my heart ♪
♪ kick-start my heart ♪
♪ Say I got trouble.
trouble in my eyes ♪
♪ I'm just looking for
another good time ♪
♪ My heart. my heart.
kick-start my heart...
How are you alive?!
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Baby...
Easy.
I just kept calm and carried on.
Help her. I've got this.
Come...
Sorry. mate.
♪ Yeah. are you
ready na-na now? ♪
♪ Whoa. yeah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart.
give it a start ♪
♪ Whoa. yeah ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Whoa...
Open the door!
♪ Give it a start...
Is it bad?
♪ Whoa. yeah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart.
hope it never stops...
-Where are we going?
-I got you.
Don't go dying on me
a third time. okay?
Oh. there's a knife in my leg!
No. wait. wait. Maybe
we should leave it in.
No. no. no. no. no.
no. no. no. no. no. no!
-Wasn't that bad.
-Good. Okay.
Sam?
Punch it!
Get down!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart... ♪
♪ Whoa. yeah ♪
♪ Baby ♪
I'm driving blind here!
Here! Sat view!
Nice.
Any other toys in
this Batmobile?
Smoke!
♪ Ooh. ah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart...
-Turn. Turn. Turn. Turn!
-I will. I will. I will.
♪ We did all of this to rock ♪
♪ Whoa. yeah...
♪ Whoa. yeah ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-B-Baby...
♪ Kick-start my heart.
hope it never stops...
The fridge!
What. are you gonna
kill them with snacks?
Backup blood supply.
Take this. you
bloody bastards!
That's the Beast.
It's the Beast!
He's got a rocket launcher!
Sam. incoming!
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Baby...
♪ Kick-start my heart ♪
You have now reached
your destination.
Effective midnight tonight.
Italy will be withdrawing
from the NATO alliance.
On behalf of the
Republic of France.
we withdraw as well.
It's with a heavy heart.
despite my most strident efforts
to hold this alliance together.
on behalf of the United States.
I withdraw our...
Hold it right there!
On behalf of the
United Kingdom...
And the United
States of America.
...take it all down
several notches. everyone.
That's right.
You're not getting
rid of us that easy.
And we're not getting rid
of this alliance that easy.
because we all have a job to do.
I get it.
You're embarrassed.
You're angry.
But we need NATO.
We need partnerships.
We need to treat each
other with respect.
embrace each other's differences
and lean into our commonalities.
To send a message to future
generations that we were here.
That we did the right thing.
And that starts by
taking the fight
to the very real
enemies we face.
There it is.
The inevitable conclusion.
The people elect a dopey actor
as leader of the free world.
Of course their
country can't survive.
And you just sealed the deal.
-These people are our partners. and we need them.
-For what?
We grow food. We pump oil.
We manufacture.
Meanwhile. we send our
people to die in their wars.
This is not a partnership.
We give. they take.
But not anymore.
The plane is going down.
We put the oxygen masks
on ourselves first.
These are all false
alliances anyway.
False alliances?
That's something you
know a lot about.
That's what kills
you most. isn't it?
It's not that I'm a better
politician than you'll ever be.
It's that I'm a better actor.
Kill them all.
Everybody. down!
Over there!
Get in here!
Get down.
Deal with her.
Now! We should go now!
That way!
No. no. no! That way! Go! Go!
Gradov!
Guys. come on! We've got to go!
-Sam!
-Will!
Noel.
Get Gradov! I got this guy.
She said she's got it.
Go.
Shoot him?
Hmm?
Get the gun.
Oh.
Whoa!
Who's the action hero now. huh?
Will!
Good to go?
Try not to kill the wall.
I got him. I got him.
He's got to be in
here somewhere.
I think he's out.
Let's dance.
Drop it.
Back up.
Back up!
There's nowhere to go.
It's over.
Not for me.
Goddamn it!
We're gonna let him get away?
We can't wait ten
years to get this guy.
We're not waiting ten years.
Do you remember at the
end of Water Cobra 2?
You said you never
saw my movies.
I know. I lied.
I've seen them all.
They're classics.
But the one moment that
really cut through them all
is when Water Cobra sacrifices
himself to save his brother.
You know what I'm talking about?
♪ Wise men say...
We go on three?
♪ Only fools...
Three!
♪ Rush in ♪
♪ but I can't help ♪
♪ falling in love ♪
♪ with you...
♪ Shall I stay? ♪
♪ Would it be a sin...
♪ If I can't help ♪
♪ falling in love ♪
♪ with you? ♪
♪ Like a river flows ♪
♪ surely to the sea ♪
♪ darling. so it goes ♪
♪ some things are meant to be...
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ take my whole life. too...
♪ For I can't help...
How's that for gym strong?
Hey!
♪ With you ♪
♪ For I can't help...
Everything harpoons
for a reason.
♪ Falling in love...
♪ With you ♪
Two months after NATO
nearly disbanded.
the alliance is making hopeful
strides in rebuilding trust.
President Derringer and
Prime Minister Clarke
have been crucial
in these efforts.
as new transparency measures
are being implemented
and there's a restored
sense of cooperation.
-Here you go.
-Cheers.
Nice.
You two gonna rekindle?
Uh. I don't know.
She's halfway around the world
on some covert operation.
We'll see how it goes.
Still a bit complicated.
Well. just talk her out of
the cons and into the pros.
Maybe she'll come around.
Actually...
you might be able to
help me with this.
"Congratulations on your big
bump in approval ratings.
Guess you're not as
poll-arizing as you thought."
Okay. so now we got to
hit her with a pun back.
Okay.
Uh. it's. um. it's. uh...
"That's nice. but it polls
in comparison to you."
You know what?
I think I'm just gonna
go with: "Thank you.
I miss you.
Hope to see you soon.
Don't get shot."
You know what? That's perfect.
Before I forget.
two tickets to a meet and
greet with Harry Styles in D.C.
It's official.
You are now the coolest
Uncle Sam I know.
Thank you. You hungry?
Oh. I'm starving.
What's good here?
I ordered us a little something.
Here you go. gents.
Okay. All right.
Fish and chips.
Dig in.
You guys. um. got
any. uh. ketchup?
No.
We do vinegar.
Yeah. these are fries.
This is not a salad.
Well. my country. my condiments.
-Mmm.
-Okay.
Okay. You know what?
Well. you come to the Oval
Office. we're doing ketchup.
Once you see the light. you're
gonna be stocking the. um...
What the hell's your
office called again?
-My office?
-Yeah.
It's called "my office."
Boy. you guys are really afraid
of spicing things up. huh?
Oh. yeah. It's really spicy to name
things after colors and shapes.
You know what I mean.
"Hey. what should we
call this white house?
-Mm. the White House?"
-Don't.
"Hey. this office is oval.
What should we call it?
I know."
The Oval Office.
-Yeah. yeah.
-That's real spicy.
Hey. you got a problem. take it
up with George Washington. okay?
He died a hundred years
before the Oval Office
was even built.
Uh. why you gonna
bust me on a technicality?
Well. technically it's
not a technicality.
It's an insignificant detail.
No. it's a fact. which is
exactly what a technicality is.
When did you become a farmer?
-'Cause you are milking this.
-Really?
Says you. the sheep
nipple aficionado?
I don't even think we
need to talk about that.
You don't want to
talk about that?
No. No. we don't.
♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ when you're not strong ♪
♪ and I'll be your friend ♪
♪ I'll help you carry on...
Did I take one for democracy?
You bet I did.
Right in the noggin.
But who would've thunk it?
This bullet hit at the exact spot
where I had the metal plate installed
after my whole
rotisserie grill debacle.
I mean. one
nanometer either way.
I am not here sipping
this Bahama Mama.
No. sir.
Am I a hero?
Sure.
Yeah. that's what the president
and prime minister say
whenever we talk on
a semi-regular basis.
And yes. there's some light chitchat
about a cabinet appointment.
No big deal.
-Yeah.
-Sure thing.
Nice try.
I believe you.
Nice to meet you. Agent Comer.
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app